Department of Mathematics fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Mathematics fonds
1965 - 1988
F-14
8.63 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Mathematics
One of the original departments of Simon Fraser University, the Department of Mathematics was opened to students in September 1965 as part of the Faculty of Science. The Department has been responsible, through its Head, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs in mathematics and statistics. In 1984 the name of the Department was changed to its present form. In 1965, there were five full and assistant professors, two instructors and one visiting lecturer. In 1986, the faculty comprised twenty professors, eleven associate professors and three assistant professors.
Initial programs offered led to the B.Sc., M.Sc. and Ph.D. in Mathematics. In 1977, a B.Sc. (honours) program was introduced. By 1986, honours programs in conjunction with other departments included Mathematical Physics, Mathematics and Computing Science, and Management and Systems Science. The original goal of the Department, which it has continued to emphasize, was to work towards excellence in pure mathematics, and in certain branches of mathematics, statistics and computing – a regimen frequently encountered in British and European universities, but at that time a rarity in North America.
Like other SFU departments, the Department of Mathematics and Statistics was organized administratively into a Head (renamed Chair in 1972), and departmental committees. While the Chair had overall responsibility to the Department and the Dean of Science for the efficient operation of the Department, most decisions were made at the committee level with major issues referred to Departmental meetings for decision. The long-standing committees of the Department were the Appointments Committee, renamed the Appointment and long-range Planning Committee; the Graduate Studies Committee; the Undergraduate Studies Committee; and the Salaries, Tenure and Promotion Committee (known also as the Departmental Tenure Committee (DTC) and the Tenure and Promotions Committee).
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
The fonds of the Department of Mathematics and Statistics consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curriculum and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; course evaluations; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, an external review, faculty files, memoranda, minutes of meetings, and reports.
When the Archives received the records, the original order imposed upon them by the Department was not evident. Accordingly, the archivist has arranged the series alphabetically to facilitate research.
Freedman, Allen R.; Graham, G. A. C.; Singh, Manohar; Reilly, Norman R.; Lardner, R. W.; Shoemaker, E. M.; Lachlan, Alistair H.; Harrop, Ronald
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Department between 1981 and 1989.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed as of September 2002 (2.67 m., 1976-1994). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventory of the Faculty of Science fonds, F-24; and the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies fonds, F-23.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- Budget, 1978 - 1982; F-14-1; 1 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of memoranda between the Department Chair, the Dean of Science, and Vice-President, Academic concerning budget allocations of the Department.
  - Operating budget, 1978 - 1982; F-14-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
- Committees - departmental, 1965 - 1986; F-14-2; 2.91 m of textual records
  Series consists of the records of departmental committees. It includes agenda, minutes, correspondence, reports and associated papers.
  Access to records in the subseries "Appointments" and "Salaries, Tenure and Promotion" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Ad hoc committee on hiring priorities, 1978 - 1980; F-14-2-1; 1 cm of textual records
    - Ad hoc committee on hiring priorities, 1978 - 1980; F-14-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
  - Appointments, 1965 - 1982; F-14-2-2; 77 cm of textual records
    - Appointments committee, 1965 - 1966; F-14-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1967; F-14-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1968; F-14-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1969; F-14-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1969; F-14-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1969; F-14-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1970; F-14-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1980; F-14-2-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1970; F-14-2-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1971; F-14-2-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1971; F-14-2-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 14-1)
    - Appointments committee, 1971; F-14-2-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1972; F-14-2-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1972; F-14-2-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1972; F-14-2-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1973; F-14-2-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1973; F-14-2-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1973; F-14-2-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1974; F-14-2-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1974; F-14-2-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1974; F-14-2-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 14-2)
    - Appointments committee, 1975; F-14-2-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 14-3)
    - Appointments committee, 1975; F-14-2-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 14-3)
    - Appointments committee, 1975; F-14-2-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 14-3)
    - Appointments committee, 1975; F-14-2-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 14-3)
    - Appointments committee, 1975; F-14-2-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 14-3)
    - Appointments committee, 1976; F-14-2-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 14-3)
    - Appointments committee, 1976; F-14-2-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1976; F-14-2-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1977; F-14-2-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1977; F-14-2-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1977; F-14-2-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1978; F-14-2-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1978; F-14-2-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1978; F-14-2-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 14-4)
    - Appointments committee, 1979; F-14-2-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments committee, 1979; F-14-2-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments committee, 1979; F-14-2-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments committee, 1980; F-14-2-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments committee, 1980; F-14-2-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments committee, 1980; F-14-2-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments committee, 1980; F-14-2-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments and long-range planning committee, 1980; F-14-2-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 14-5)
    - Appointments and long-range planning committee, 1981; F-14-2-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 14-6)
    - Appointments and long-range planning committee, 1981; F-14-2-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 14-6)
    - Appointments and long-range planning committee, 1981; F-14-2-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 14-6)
    - Appointments and long-range planning committee, 1982; F-14-2-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 14-6)
    - Appointments and long-range planning committee, 1982; F-14-2-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 14-6)
    - Appointments and long-range planning committee, 1966 - 1981; F-14-2-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 14-6)
    - Correspondence - A.S. Farooqui - includes 2 tapes of Peak interview, Singh/Farooqui (Nov.26, 1980), 1967 - 1982; F-14-2-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 14-6)
    - Correspondence - Farooqui, A.S., 1976 - 1980; F-14-2-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Correspondence with Dr. Farooqui, 1975 - 1978; F-14-2-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
  - Grauduate studies, 1969 - 1986; F-14-2-3; 36 cm of textual records
    - Graduate studies committee, 1969; F-14-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1969; F-14-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1970; F-14-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1970; F-14-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1970; F-14-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1970 - 1971; F-14-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1971; F-14-2-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1971; F-14-2-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-7)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1971; F-14-2-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1972; F-14-2-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1972; F-14-2-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1972; F-14-2-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee rational for proposed changed in graduate regulations, F-14-2-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1974; F-14-2-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 14-8)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1974; F-14-2-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1975; F-14-2-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1975; F-14-2-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1976; F-14-2-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1976; F-14-2-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1976; F-14-2-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1981 - 1983; F-14-2-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
    - Graduate studies committee, 1984 - 1986; F-14-2-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 14-9)
  - Salaries, tenure and promotion, 1966 - 1986; F-14-2-4; 1.13 m of textual records
    - Tenure committee index (tenure and promotions and policies), 1968 - 1970; F-14-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee summary minutes, 1968 - 1969; F-14-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure and promotions policies, 1968 - 1969; F-14-2-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1968 - 1969; F-14-2-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1969 - 1970; F-14-2-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1970; F-14-2-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1970; F-14-2-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1970; F-14-2-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1971; F-14-2-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1971; F-14-2-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1971; F-14-2-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 14-10)
    - Tenure committee, 1972; F-14-2-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1972; F-14-2-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1972; F-14-2-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1973; F-14-2-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1973; F-14-2-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1974; F-14-2-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1974; F-14-2-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1974; F-14-2-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 14-11)
    - Tenure committee, 1975; F-14-2-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 14-12)
    - Tenure committee, 1975; F-14-2-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 14-12)
    - Tenure committee, 1975; F-14-2-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 14-12)
    - Tenure committee, 1976; F-14-2-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 14-12)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1976; F-14-2-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 14-12)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1977; F-14-2-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 14-12)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1977; F-14-2-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 14-12)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1977; F-14-2-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1977; F-14-2-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 14-13)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Tenure/promotions salaries, 1979; F-14-2-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1979; F-14-2-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1979; F-14-2-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1979; F-14-2-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1979; F-14-2-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1980; F-14-2-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1980; F-14-2-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 14-14)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1980; F-14-2-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1980; F-14-2-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1981; F-14-2-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1981; F-14-2-4-0-46 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1981; F-14-2-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1981; F-14-2-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1982; F-14-2-4-0-49 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1982; F-14-2-4-0-50 (Archival box - standard 14-15)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1982; F-14-2-4-0-51 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1982 - 1983; F-14-2-4-0-52 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1982 - 1983; F-14-2-4-0-53 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1982 - 1983; F-14-2-4-0-54 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1983; F-14-2-4-0-55 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1983; F-14-2-4-0-56 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1984; F-14-2-4-0-57 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1984; F-14-2-4-0-58 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1984; F-14-2-4-0-59 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1985; F-14-2-4-0-60 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1985; F-14-2-4-0-61 (Archival box - standard 14-16)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1985; F-14-2-4-0-62 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Salaries, tenure and promotions, 1985; F-14-2-4-0-63 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Department tenure committee, 1984 - 1985; F-14-2-4-0-64 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Tenure committee - D, 1966 - 1972; F-14-2-4-0-65 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Tenure committee - R, 1966 - 1973; F-14-2-4-0-66 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Tenure committee - S, 1966 - 1973; F-14-2-4-0-67 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Salary review materials, 1982 - 1986; F-14-2-4-0-68 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Salary review materials, 1984; F-14-2-4-0-69 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Salary review materials, 1984; F-14-2-4-0-70 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Tenure committee (faculty) - A-B, 1966 - 1979; F-14-2-4-0-71 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Tenure committee (faculty) - B-E, 1966 - 1979; F-14-2-4-0-72 (Archival box - standard 14-17)
    - Tenure committee (faculty) - F-H, 1966 - 1979; F-14-2-4-0-73 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Tenure committee (faculty) - S, 1966 - 1979; F-14-2-4-0-74 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Tenure committee (faculty) - S, 1966 - 1979; F-14-2-4-0-75 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Tenure committee (faculty) - T, 1966 - 1979; F-14-2-4-0-76 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Tenure committee (faculty) - V-W, 1966 - 1979; F-14-2-4-0-77 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Department tenure committee - T, B, 1977 - 1978; F-14-2-4-0-78 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Department tenure committee - R, 1981; F-14-2-4-0-79 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Tenure and promotions - L, 1978; F-14-2-4-0-80 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
    - Tenure and promotions - R, 1976 - 1978; F-14-2-4-0-81 (Archival box - standard 14-18)
  - Tutorial, 1974; F-14-2-5; 1 cm of textual records
    - Tutorial committee, 1974; F-14-2-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
  - Undergraduate studies, 1970 - 1986; F-14-2-6; 63 cm of textual records
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1970; F-14-2-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1971; F-14-2-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1971; F-14-2-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-14-2-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-14-2-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1972; F-14-2-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 14-19)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1973; F-14-2-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, other programs non-Mathematics, 1973 - 1974; F-14-2-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, transfers Mathematics program, 1973 - 1974; F-14-2-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974; F-14-2-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974; F-14-2-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974; F-14-2-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 14-20)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974; F-14-2-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 14-21)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974 - 1975; F-14-2-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 14-21)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1974 - 1975; F-14-2-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 14-21)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1975; F-14-2-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 14-21)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1975; F-14-2-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 14-21)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1975; F-14-2-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 14-21)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1976; F-14-2-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1976; F-14-2-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1976; F-14-2-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1977; F-14-2-6-0-28 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1977; F-14-2-6-0-29 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1977; F-14-2-6-0-30 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, calendar changes - file 1, 1978 - 1979; F-14-2-6-0-31 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, calendar changes - file 2, 1978; F-14-2-6-0-32 (Archival box - standard 14-22)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, calendar changes - file 3, 1977 - 1978; F-14-2-6-0-33 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1978; F-14-2-6-0-34 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1978; F-14-2-6-0-35 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1978; F-14-2-6-0-36 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1979; F-14-2-6-0-37 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1979; F-14-2-6-0-38 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1979; F-14-2-6-0-39 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1981 - 1982; F-14-2-6-0-40 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1983 - 1984; F-14-2-6-0-41 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
    - Undergraduate studies committee, 1985 - 1986; F-14-2-6-0-42 (Archival box - standard 14-23)
- Committees - Faculty of Science, 1965 - 1971; F-14-3; 5 cm of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence relating to various Faculty of Science committees.
  Access to records in this series is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.